<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Science Portfolio on Aishwarya Kshirsagar</title>
    <link>https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Science Portfolio on Aishwarya Kshirsagar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BankBot Using NLP</title>
      <link>https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/post/chapter2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/post/chapter2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this report, I have explained the implementation of the code and methods that I have used to build a BankBot.
Summary So What is a Chat Bot or to be specific a Bank Bot? A chatbot or chatterbot is a software application used to conduct an online chat conversation via text or text-to-speech. Chatbots are used in dialog systems for various purposes including customer service, request routing, or information gathering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/contact/</guid>
      <description>Linked In https://www.linkedin.com/in/aishwarya-kshirsagar-9b57471a0/
Kaggle https://www.kaggle.com/aishwaryakshirsagar
GitHub https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid 19 Spread Prevention</title>
      <link>https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>Event - India Academia Connect and Nvidia AI Hackathon This Project is a part of NVIDIA and Academia AI Hackathon which was held in October, 2021.
Goal → COVID-19 Spread Prevention Training Score → Accuracy 98% Team → Data Pirates🏴‍☠️ Our Team was ranked 7th in this event all over India. Problem Description: COVID-19 Spread Prevention using Computer Vision and Deep Learning
Social Distance Detection- Social distancing is deliberately increasing the physical space between people to avoid spreading illness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Similarity Detection using NLP and Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://github.com/AishwaryaKshirsagar/AishwaryaKshirsagar1/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this report, I have explained the implementation of the code and methods that I have used to find similarity between the texts in the two columns in an unsupervised manner.
Summary The dataset provided includes Unique Id, and the two columns of texts. Similarity scores were to be calculated between the texts of columns 1 and 2. Since the labels for the texts were not provided. I opted for unsupervised way to get the results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
